sup everyone came with woody 45 he was a
very that's a video so some of you may
know that just we switched the new
trailer for the latest back Batman I'll
can gaining just came out and I decide
you know what up I love me we all love
us some superhero but I love I love me
some green lines of Martian Manhunter
hmm and we all loved it we all love that
dick dick grayson you know Robert oh my
God I especially loved it oh I love
playing birthday so I hope dick
Grayson's gonna be playable character in
this game which I heard he my BF not
winning I appreciate it Kim something
you drop dead right of us Robin Batman
and now we will all go breathe in this
new game playable I don't know I hotel
tada I wanted to play with dead I want
to play with Batman's dick so so [ __ ]
bad well I get you in these Supermans
dick to go for those who don't pull off
you don't know Robin happy like the
batting he runs you Superman Superman is
the one who told us he come that way
yeah I'm gonna haul oh God don't tell me
I know how much I love t20 well I loved
Mississippi how long is it easier for
example hold on my friend into and you
can see I love you Savannah I am forever
boy I love Superman Maura look at that
he never won Superman suit might be the
refugees here food clapping batman game
anyway
I think you get all breathing out go see
man but let's get to reacting the new
trailer now to be honest I haven't
really played any of a badman games
because let's face it super your games
I'll slug I mean though I'm going
through my 64 gay animal 73 in 321
Reggie dance mature hoping if you rub
Robbie like poop on magazine oh my God
oh there's a badminton little clock hey
babe my coming out [ __ ] was robbed you
come home I don't care that the side
kids and Dick Grayson with my dick all
Bevins got beat did way their own
beating his ass oh no I get something
running up might be Superman in disguise
well is good graces oh oh oh all the
Batman and wake him up to be just knit
Superman ass oh my God oh no [ __ ]
wife Batman Robin and I'm looking gal to
beat some ass oh my God you got your
play these games Who am I kidding hemas
not better he mends the only cool long
what's good man come on show more dick
come on what is the reason for those who
don't know deep Grayson he's a sick see
Robin d grapes in there Anna West yeah 3
by foot while and then Adam West yeah oh
[ __ ] [ __ ] tank only aa bad man beats
a man is they run playable he'd been
playa working with Kevin oh oh yeah he's
cool i'll see you there ah I'll a give
good the Superman logo game of Twister
man game God I make the game so much
cool Oh be the fat man I'm June 23rd so
cool right there one down time of year
for the new Batman hey gonna go watch
some Superman mask gotta go watch
something good like a scene that crabby
fail gotta help on a play over I'm a
kiss again he is nice [ __ ] new minute
video of it in a few days